（歓声）
（古奈）入りました！→
It's in bounds!
まさかの返球に　チーム六騎聖
一歩も動けず。→
An unbelievable return shot left the
Six Holy Knights frozen in place!
これで石矢魔の退学は
白紙になりました！
And with this, the Ishiyama
students' expulsion is rescinded!
（ヒルダ）坊っちゃま。
（古市）よっしゃ～！
Yes!
（邦枝）いい試合だったわ。また
やりましょう。
It was a good game. Let's
do it again sometime.
（出馬）まあ　君らには
まだ　これから…。
Sure. You're still going...
（古奈）あ　ちょ…何ですか
あなた！
Wait! What do you think you're doing?!
（霧矢）
スポーツを通じて一致団結
流れる汗　ほとばしる情熱。→
All are equals on the sports field.
All drench themselves in sweat.
All overflow with passion!
クソ似合わね～事
してんじゃね～ぞ　男鹿！
That crap don't suit you,
so don't do it, Oga!
Finally, the Deciding Battle!
（ベル坊）ニョ？
あいつは…。
That's...
（三木）霧矢？
フ…驚いたぜ男鹿！テメーが→
Kiriya!
You surprise me, Oga.
Never thought you'd end up
at a school like this...
こんな学校にいるとはよ。しかも
天下の不良校→
And the top members of the Ishiyama
gang playin' volleyball?!
石矢魔のトップ達が
揃いも揃って→
バレーだあ？くだらね～事
してんじゃねえよ。
Why are you wastin' your
time with this crap?!
（神崎）ああ？
（姫川）んだと　コラ。
Huh?
What was that?!
あ？
出てってもらえるか　ここは
君みたいのが来る所やない。
Would you mind leaving?
This is no place for someone like you.
残念だったな
六騎聖の兄ちゃん。
I'm sorry to hear that, Mr. 6 Holy Knight...
≪おら　騒ぐんじゃね～よ≫
（霧矢）テメーらの出番はね～よ。→
Alla' ya's pipe down!
You've got nothin' to do here.
Everybody in this gym is our hostage.
ここにいる全員が人質だ。
≪ぶっ潰されて～か≫
You wanna get your ass kicked?!
（バン！）
分かったら
おとなしくしてな。
If you see my point, be a good little boy.
何なの　あいつ。
マムシの霧矢。
Who the hell is he?
Kiriya, the Viper...
え？
魔野中にいた有名な不良っす。
He was a notorious thug
back in Mano Middle School.
だいぶ前に
引っ越したはずなんすけど。
But he moved away a long time ago...
男鹿と何かあったの？
Did something happen between him and Oga?
何が目的だ！霧矢。
What the hell do you want, Kiriya?!
あ？テメー　どっかで会ったか？
Have I met you somewhere before, punk?
何？
（男鹿）おい。俺に何か用か？
What?!
Hey!
You got business with me?
用？生ぬるい事
言ってんじゃね～ぞ　男鹿。→
"Business"? What, you talk
like a wuss now, Oga?
俺はテメーの人生を
ぶっ壊しに来たんだよ。
I came here to demolish your life...
そうか。
アブ。
Is that right?
いいか　聞けこら。俺が　どんだけ
この日を待ち望んだか。
Hey! Listen to me!
You know how long I've
waited for this day...?!
テメーに受けた
この傷の恨みと屈辱を…。
To pay you back for these
scars and the humiliation...
オオオアオ…。
って邪魔だ！
Get that out of the way!
フ。
うるせ～！
（霧矢）ぐ…。
Shut up!
久々に　いい感じの凶悪なヤローが
来たと思ったけど→
It's been a while since I thought
I found a real evil bastard...
…期待外れ！
ダブ～！
ええ。
But you disappoint me!
（ざわめき）
（三鏡）おい　ね～ちゃん。
はい。
Hey, girly!
Yes?
（三鏡）
このゴハンくん焼きおにぎりの
１２００円って　明らかに→
1200 yen for cute grilled rice
balls?! That's ridiculous!
高すぎんだろ～。
８００円くらいに　まけてよ～。
I'll pay you 800 for 'em.
も　申し訳ありませんが…。
（鬼塚）三鏡　連絡だ。→
I-I'm sorry, but...
Mikagami...
We got the word. Sounds like
Kiriya's gettin' started.
霧矢が始めたらしいぞ。
（黒木）行きますよ。
Let's go.
（三鏡）
え～！せめて
あれ食ってからにしてよ～。→
At least let me have a snack first...
つ～か誰か金貸して。
諦めて下さい。
Somebody, let me borrow some money.
Please, drop it.
（出崎）や～ね。あんた
どんだけ貧乏よ。
Jesus. How poor are you?
I'll make you grilled rice balls later on.
焼きおにぎりなら　後で
ワシが作ってやる。
（霧矢）
クク…。相変わらずだな　男鹿。
テメーは　そうでなくちゃ→
You never change, Oga.
But that's what makes gettin'
revenge on you worth it.
復讐のしがいがね～ってもんだ。
ガルルル…。
手はじめに　そうだな
お前　退学になっとくか。
For starters, let's see...
I think I'll have you get expelled.
あ？
（霧矢）さっきの試合　退学が
かかってたんだってな～。→
That's what was ridin' on your
volleyball game, wasn't it?
勝って一安心って　とこだろうが
残念だったな。
You won, you breathed a sigh of relief...
But too bad. I showed up.
ぜ～んぶ　台無しだ。
殴ったもんな～今→
All your efforts just went out the window.
You just clocked me in front of everybody.
全員の見てる前で。おい
ど～なんだ先公！
Hey! What do you think about that, teach?!
暴力沙汰だよな。
（木戸）
そこまでのものじゃないだろ。
It was an act of violence, wasn't it?
I wouldn't go that far.
ああ？ふざけんなよ。
（木戸）だが　まあ…。
Hah?! What are you, blind?!
But... if I hear any more threats,
there certainly will be consequences.
これ以上の脅迫行為は　確かに→
処罰の対象になるな。もちろん
貴様らもだ→
Of course, that goes for you too, Teimou.
帝毛
他校に乗り込んでのケンカ等→
Storming into another school and fighting
will be reported to the police.
警察沙汰だぞ。
だよね～ボクちゃんも→
Sure, right?
Man, I'm so scared to get
expelled, maybe I'll go home...
退学は怖いし帰ろっかな～。
な～んて言うかボケ！
As if...
Like I'd say that?!
男鹿！
どうでもいいんだよ　そんなもん。
Oga!
I don't give a crap about that!
退学だろ～がケーサツだろうが…。
テメーを道連れに出来んなら→
Expulsion, the cops...
If I can bring you down with
me, I don't care where I go.
オレは　どこにだって行くぜ！
《手を出す。テメーは絶対…》
道連れ？
Hit me.
You will hit me...
Bring me down with you?
１人で行ってろ。バーカ。
Go by yourself, dumbass.
う…。
（夏目）待て。ここで飛び出したら→
Hold it.
If you go out there, you'll make
Oga-chan's self-restraint meaningless.
男鹿ちゃんの我慢が無駄に
なっちゃうよ。バレーでの勝利も。
The volleyball victory, too...
だけど…。
But...
男鹿ちゃんが耐えてるのに
オレらがキレる訳には→
If Oga-chan can keep himself in
check, we can't afford to flip out.
いかないでしょ。
男鹿。
Oga...
ど～したよ　男鹿。ずいぶん
おとなしいじゃね～か。
What's wrong, Oga?
You're not makin' a peep.
ま　このままテメーを沈めんのも
悪くね～か。
Well, guess it wouldn't be so bad
to just beat you senseless...
…アイ。
心配すんな　ベル坊。
Don't worry, Beel.
こんな野郎の攻撃　蚊ほども
効きゃしね～よ。
Attacks from a jackass like this
aren't even as bad as mosquito bites.
…おい！
Hey!
いいぜ。その強がりが
いつまで続くか試してやるよ。
Now we're talkin'.
Let's see how long you
can keep toughin' it out.
いい加減に　しろ！
That's enough...
outta you!
おいおい　なんちゅ～突きだよ。
テメー話　聞いてたか？
Hey, what the hell'd you do to my bat?
You were listenin' before, right?
ここにいる生徒達が
ど～なっても…。
（三木）僕を忘れたか　霧矢！
You don't care what happens
to all these students?
Fight me, Kiriya!
あ？
（三木）何で今更
復讐なんだ。
Why are you getting revenge now?
大体…。
It was...
３年前の復讐だってんなら
僕も相手にするべきだろう！
If you're getting revenge for three years
ago, you should be fighting me, too!
…バカが。
Idiot...
あ～もしかして　お前
あん時　男鹿と一緒にいた。
Were you there with Oga back then?
あ　そ～だ　そ～だ。間違いねえ。
Oh yeah, that's right. Sure of it.
その傷　オレが
つけたんだもんな。あんまり→
I gave you those wounds, didn't I?
You were such a small fry I forgot about you.
小物だったんで
忘れちまってたよ。
何？
何で今更かって？
What?!
Why now, you ask?
Didn't have much choice.
Family matters, you see.
しょ～がね～だろ
家庭の事情ってやつだ。
あの後すぐに
引っ越しちまったからな～。
I moved away right afterwards.
…奈良に。
《あ…奈良？僕と同じ》
To Nara.
Nara?
That's the same as me...
だが　オレは受けた屈辱は忘れねえ
どこまでも→
But I don't forget the
humiliation I received.
I don't care how long it takes to
chase you down, I'll make you pay.
くらいついて
必ず後悔させてやる。
だから　こうして戻って来た訳よ。
So, that's why I'm back like this.
《もし　男鹿が
それを知っていたとしたら？→
If Oga knew about that...
自分の目の届かない所で　必ず
霧矢が仕返しに来ると→
If he knew Kiriya would come for revenge
in a place he couldn't reach...
分かっていたら…》
遅ぇぞ　テメーら。
You guys are late!
わりい　わりい。共学の学祭って
初めてで楽しくてよ。
Sorry, our bad.
It was our first school wide
festival, so we were having fun!
What? You aren't fighting yet?
何だ　まだケンカになって
おらんではないか。
こいつが男鹿ですか？
That's Oga, but...
But there's got to be
some mistake. He's tiny.
ど～見ても違うでしょ？チビだし。
なんすか　あいつら。
帝毛の影組。やはり→
Who are they?
Teimo's Shadow Group.
As I figured, they're
working for the Viper now.
マムシの下に　ついてたか。
あ…。
I was a fool!
((つ～かさ。お前　誰だっけ？))
So yeah... Who are you, again?
Stop acting like you know me... Who are you?
((馴れ馴れしいんだよ。
誰だ　お前))
《本当の事を確かめもせず…》
And I never found out the truth...
（三木）
《男鹿を憎んでいたなんて》
I hated Oga?!
((すっこんでろ！弱ぇくせに。→
Get outta here, weakling!
目障りなんだよ！))
Yer an eyesore!
《ずっと
守られていたっていうのに》
But he was always just protecting me!
ハ…くたばりなさい！
Now, die!
く…。
くたばんのは　テメーらだ！
You're the one's...
...who're gonna get it
ダ～ブ！
な…。
《あ～あ。やっちまった》
しょ～がねえ。テメーとの勝負は
お預けだ。
あ…。
Ah well, guess we'll have
to fight some other time.
とっとと片付けんぞ　三木。
Let's clean these guys out already, Miki.
《…名前を》
My name...
Ah well, guess we'll have
to fight some other time.
しょ～がねえ。テメーとの勝負は
お預けだ。
あ…。
Let's clean these guys out already, Miki.
とっとと片付けんぞ　三木。
《…名前を》
He...
I want to get stronger!
（三木）((強くなりたいんです。
僕は…→
I want to be someone that
people can look up to!
背中を任せられる
人間になりたいんです))
Hisaya...
（出馬）
《久也…それが
強さを求めた理由やったな》
If that's the reason you seek strength...
I think that's the first time
you've called me by my name.
（三木）初めてだな
君に名前を呼ばれたのは。
あ？
But... Could you call me "Hisaya", instead?
でも　どうせなら
久也って呼んでくれないか？
No way.
やだ。
なっ！どうしてだよ！
Why not?!
'cause that's gross, dude.
いや　気持ち悪りぃし。
Gross?
気持ち悪い！？ブエエ　ウエエ。
キヒヒヒ　取り込み中　悪いが
よそ見してる暇は　ね～ぜ。
Sorry to interrupt, but you don't
have time to be getting distracted.
あ～ん　眼鏡が台無し。
ん！ん！
My glasses are ruined.
（一同）ああ…。
They're not intimidated at all!
（静）
やつら…全然　こたえてない…！
そいつらは影組。オレが来るまで
帝毛を支配していた武闘派たち。
They're the Shadow Group. They're the
warring faction that ruled Teimo before I showed up.
いわば帝毛の四天王だ。
They're like, the Four Kings of Teimo.
へ！
The Baldy Group?
ハゲ組！？
おい　こら！
Hey, you! We get that all the
time, but don't misunderstand!
わかりやすく
間違えてんじゃね～よ！
こりゃスキンヘッドだ！
ファッションなんだよ！
This is a skinhead! It's fashion!
いや　わしはハゲじゃ。
Yeah, but I'm bald.
Yeah, so am I.
ええ　私も。
うん。
Yup.
裏切り者～！
You traitors!
キヒヒ　強え～ぞ　こいつらは。
These guys are strong.
まあ　せいぜい　てめえら２人は→
Now you two have a nice little fight
with them and get yourselves expelled.
仲良くケンカして　退学にでも
なってくれや。
Hold it!
待ちなさい！
そういうことなら加勢するわよ。
I'll help you out!
No can do, Shizuka-san.
アカンで　静さん。
これは久也の戦いや。
This is Hisaya's fight.
そうっすよ。邦枝先輩。
それに忘れたんですか？人質。
That's right, Kunieda-senpai. Plus,
did you forget about the hostage?
その通りだぜ　姐ちゃん。
てめえらが下手に動けば→
That's right.
If you guys make one wrong move, the entire
student body's gonna be wrapped up in it.
全校生徒が巻き添えを食う。
If you want to, just stay
put, watch, and learn.
そうしたくなかったら
そこでアホ面下げて見てろよ。
下手に動けば…な。
One wrong move, eh?
Izuma-kun...
出馬くん。
やりはじめたら　どうせ→
When they start at it, people
are gonna watch, for sure.
２人に目が行くやろ。
いいのね？
オレらだけじゃ
手が足りひんからな。
You sure?
I couldn't handle them all myself.
おい　あっちのデカイのと
チャラいのは俺がやる。
Hey.
I'll handle that big guy and the lightweight.
てめえは　そっちの２人だ。
You take the two over there.
After the attack we head toward Kiriya.
そっこうで沈めて
霧矢に行くぞ。出来るか？
You up for it?
ああ。
Yeah!
（三木）ふっふ。
ハァ…やれやれ
なめられたものですね。
Sheesh... Looks like they're
underestimating us.
あなたも何やら武術の心得が
あるようですが→
If does seem like you know some
fighting techniques, however...
先ほどの一撃で実力の違いも
分からなかったのですか？
Couldn't you tell the difference in our
strength just from that 1 previous attack?
You sure you wanna look away?
（三鏡）よそ見しててい～のかよ。
16 Heat Waves!
十六烈破～！
Death Trigger!
デストレイラー！
男鹿！
んん～！
Finished yet?
終わりか？
な！
あ！
う～！
Special attack!
必殺！！
ダーブ！
ダァー！
Super Burying Punch!
スーパーめりこみパンチ！
True Dark Death Warbler!
真　冥鶯殺！
あ…ああ。
ひ　ひいぃ！
（寧々・由加・飛鳥）ああ…。
ひ…ひ…。
う…うう。
ああ…。
ブヒー。
Don't tell me... Was that
your new special move?
まさか　今のが新しい必殺技？
おう！名付けて
スーパーめりこみパンチだ。ダーブ！
Yeah. I call it my Super Burying Punch.
Didn't all you do is add super to the name?
スーパー付けただけじゃ
ね～か。
やるじゃね～か！
まさか　ここまでとはな。
Not bad...
Didn't think it'd come to this...
But playtime is over.
だが　お遊びは終わりだ。
こっちには人質が…。
I still have my hostage-...
あ　あれ？
Sorry. We already finished.
（出馬）残念やけど　もう終いやで。
あ？
はあ！？
Disgusting pigs!
（由加）ブサイクが！
Impossible! How did they,
in such a short time?
ば　馬鹿な…。
こんな短時間に　どうやって…？
どこまでも食らいついて
後悔させてやるとか言ってたな。
You said something about chasing
you down and making you pay, right?
あ…ああ…。
おもしれえ。やってみろよ。
Interesting. Go ahead and try.
だがなぁ。
But I'll have you know...
これ以上　オレの周りをうろちょろして　めざわりなマネしてみろ。
Just try and hang around
near me and act like a pain.
あ…！
あ…。
後悔すんのは　てめえの方だ…！
あ　悪魔！
You're the one who'll regret it!
A demon!
Let's go all out, for a change, Baby Beel!
久々に全開だ　ベル坊！
ダァ！
や　やめ…！
Don't!
Zebel Blast!
ゼブラブラスト～！
ぎゃああああ！！
うおおお！
（帝毛たち）うわあああ！
What... was that?
なに…これ？
（一同）おお…。
まさか…。
Don't tell me...
ひっ…！
起きろ。かすっただけだろ。
Wake up. I just grazed you.
寝たフリしてんじゃね～よ。
Don't go playin' possum on me.
《なんだ　こいつ
ありえねえ　ありえねえぞ》
What's with him? I can't
believe this, not at all!
《オレは　とんでもねえ奴に
手ぇ出しちまったんじゃ…》
３・２・１。
I've gotten myself in real...
Wait, I know! I'll get up, it's just...
ま　待て！分かった。起きるよ。
うわああ！
Okay! I'm awake!
今すぐ全員　連れて失せろ。
Take everyone and get outta here, all of you.
ああ…ああ。
悪魔…いや。
でね～と次は…。
Demon...
And if you don't, then...
全員　黒こげにするぞぉ！
ダーウ。
I'll turn everyone into mincemeat!
ひいひいヒャッヒャッヒャ。
ダブダブダブ。
The Demon King!
魔王だ！
フフフハハハ！
うわ～！
き　霧矢さん！
K-Kiriya-san!
Dad! Dad! The Demon King is coming!
パパー！パパー！魔王が来るよ～。
あ～！ママ　助けて～！
Save me, Mommy!
《かわいそうに…つ～か》
I feel sorry for the guy.
さ　さっきの何だったの？床こげてるし。
What was that just now?
The floor's burnt...
あの人　あんなペイントしてたぁ？
That guy's got facepaint on?
《さすがにやばいな。今回は言い訳出来るような状況じゃねえぞ》
Now, this is trouble.
We can't go making excuses
to get out of this one...
（ざわめき）
I've had a feeling about this for a while...
《前々から　そんな気はしてたけどやっぱりあの子　普通じゃない》
But that kid really isn't normal!
（ざわめき）
（拍手）
は～い　全員　拍手～。
Okay you all, a round of applause.
Wow, that was amazing.
（出馬）いや～すごかったな～→
スペシャルプログラム
ケンカイリュージョン。
Our special program, "Fighting Illusion"!
なんや　みんな　きょとんとして。
What're you all doing standing
there slack jawed, people?
ほんまもんのケンカかと
思ったんか？
You all thought it was a real fight?
ちゃうちゃう。最後の特殊効果で
気付く思たけどな。
Nope, not at all.
I figured you would have caught on with
the special effects from that last attack.
≪と　特殊効果！？≫
≪え？やらせだったってこと？≫
S-Special effects?
Y-You mean you were putting us on?
なあ　静さん。
え？
Yeah, Shizuka-san.
This trick sure took a lot of
work to set up, isn't that right?
えらい苦労して
作ったもんな～この仕掛け。
そうね…でも大成功よ！みなさん！
Right.
But it was a great success!
Everyone, let's give a
great big round of applause
協力して下さった帝毛高校の
方たちにも盛大な拍手を！
to the people from
Teimo High for helping, too!
What's this?
なんだなんだ。
だまされたぞ～！
We were totally fooled!
（マイク：出馬）そして本日の主役を
張ってくれた→
And the star of today's event,
男鹿親子に
もう一度　盛大な拍手を。
The Oga family! Another
big round of applause!
すごかったぞ～！
It was amazing!
Baby, look at me!
≪赤ちゃ～ん　こっち向いて～！≫
おう！ダダ！
Is that so?
そういうことかよ。
あの野郎。いつの間に。
When did he...
ふ～ん。
大丈夫か？三木。
You okay, Miki?
あ…。
Yeah...
ああ！
You owe me for today.
今日のところは貸しにしといた。あ？
You can't go showing your
demon power that much...
アカンで…悪魔の力
あんまり見せびらかしたら。
お前…！
You're...
（由加）は～。→
We managed to avoid getting
expelled, at least.
何とか退学は免れましたね～。
You know, it's always so lonely
after the end of school festivals...
なんか～学園祭も終わりかと思うと　さみしくなるっすね。
（寧々）姐さん　遅いわね。
どこ行ったのかしら。
Madam Aoi is late.
I wonder where she went?
ん～ついに男鹿っちに告白とか。
Maybe she finally went to
Oga's place to confess!
She couldn't have!
まさか！！
いや～冗談っすよ。
Hey, I was just kidding.
（飛鳥）縁起でもね～冗談いうなよ。
Don't joke about something like that...
なんつ～か　謎っすよね。
（寧々）何が？
It's strange, you know?
What is?
（由加）男鹿っちっす。赤ん坊
連れて嫁と学校　来たり→
It's Oga. He brings a baby and his
wife to school, fights like a demon,
ケンカがオニ強かったり→
メガネ会長と　いつの間にか
たくらんでたり…。
and somehow had time to plot
with the glasses boss guy?
I can't think that scuffle
before was all an act.
さっきの騒ぎだって
仕掛けとは思えなかったっすよ。
悪魔の力…
確かに　そう言ったのか？
Demon's power? You sure that's what he said?
何もんだ　あの野郎。
お前の仲間じゃね～のかよ。
What is he? Is he a friend of yours?
Ooh, a school festival!
（早乙女）お～お～学園祭か。
なつかしいな。
This brings back memories.
I wonder if that problem-child of mine
is having a good time goin' wild...
（早乙女）うちの問題児どもは
元気に暴れてるかな？
Finally, that man comes around!
The man with the same Zebel Spell as Oga!
The guy that once looked after Tojo?
Zen-san, I've been hoping to see you.
The carpenter?
That's Gen-san.
That jack of all trades?
That's Gin-san.
On the next Beelzebub:
That Man was a Teacher!
I know! It's the awkward person!
That's Ken-san!
Plus this joke is too old, kids won't get it!
For those kids who don't
get it, ask your parents.